# Ekhande Jitendra

## Associate Product Manager

#### **OBJECTIVE**

Experience in management and consulting for 3 years in ERP and SAAS industries. I've worked as a business analyst for at least 1 years, and I managed products for past 2 year. a track record of inspiring teams from all disciplines to create and market great products. a strong analytical and problem-solving capacity. a strong background in managing backlogs, user stories, and product strategy.

#### **EXPERIENCE**

#### **SYSTEM ENGINEER (ANALYST) - DB SCHENKER**

Oct 2022 - Current

- Work with cross functional team engineering, design and marketing.
- Creating Product RoadMap and Backlog Management.
- Assist the Project Manager in managing project resources, such as people, equipment, and materials.
- Interview customers, prospects, partners, analysts, and stakeholders to gather information and feedback.
- Supporting the Project Manager and coordinating with Stakeholders.

#### SAP CONSULTANT - ALITER BUSINESS SOLUTIONS

Feb 2022 - June 2022

- Led the development and launch of a new web app that was developed for enhancing user experience in SAP.
- Managed a team of 5 engineers and designers.
- Worked with stakeholders to gather requirements and define the product roadmap.
- Increase working efficiency 20 % and eliminate human error in document posting.
- Successfully launched the app on time and within budget.

## ANALYST - BUNGE INDIA PRIVET LIMITED

Sept 2021 - Jan 2022

- Analyze, propose solution and resolve system issue.
- Support the current MM business processes and design.
- Conduct SAP MM process configuration.
- Shall possess an analytical mind and is able to see interlinkages with system solutions and usability.
- Resolve incidents in accordance to the project.
- schedule/Service Level Agreement.

#### **BUSINESS ANALYST - CANOPUS SOFTWARE SOLUTION**

May 2020 - Aug 2021

- Gather and analyze data.
- Define and document requirements.
- Develop business cases.
- Collaborate with stakeholders.
- Conduct user acceptance testing.
- Provide support and training.
- Continuous improvement.





#### CONTACT

Jeetekhande.97@amail.com 7709302716

JITENDRA (Jeetu) EKHANDE L LinkedIn

Nashik, Maharashtra

#### **EDUCATION**

SVIT Chincholi, Nashik **Mechanical Engineering** 2020

PDVVP Poly Loni, Pravaranagar Diploma Mech, Engg.

## COURCES / CERTIFICATION

Fellowship Program -Grow Junction - Product Management

Virtual Experience Program -JP Morgan - Agile Development Program

Udemy -

A To Z Product management

SAP LAB Germany – Global Certification Sourcing and Procurement

#### MANAGEMENT SKILLS

- Product Development and
- Management
- Agile Methodologies
- Problem Solving
- Data Analysis
- Cross-functional Team Management
- Teamwork
- Continuous improvement
- Stakeholder management

#### IT SKILLS

- SAP ERP SAP MM, SAP EWM
- SQL, Chat Gpt 3.5
- SAP Enable Now
- JIRA, Trello, Asana, Service Now
- Computer Basics, MS Office, MS Excel
- Balsamiq, Canva, Figma